spfldcol.edu 2012-11-20

# Springfield College Privacy Policy

## Springfield College's Commitment to Privacy

**Updated May 7, 2009**   
Springfield College is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to its Website, http://www.springfieldcollege.edu. We also believe that it is important for visitors to know how Springfield College will handle the information that we collect from them. 

The following information explains what type of information Springfield College collects from visitors to its website. 

### Information We Collect

**We collect the following information from you when you visit our site:**

  * The name of the domain through which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com if you use America Online)
  * The date and time you access our site
  * The Internet address from which you linked to our site (the Web page you "clicked" from to get to our Web site)
  * The unique address of the computer you used to access our site.

We use this information to administer our Web site, to help diagnose and troubleshoot potential server malfunctions, and to gather broad demographic information. 

**Springfield College also collects personally identifiable information (PII) at various points on our Web site.** Personally identifiable information is that which contains personal information that can be associated with an individual, such as a visitor’s name, street address, or phone number. This information may be added to Springfield College’s databases and be used for correspondence or other uses. Springfield College may also use such information to provide users with information concerning College events. 

**In some cases, Springfield College may also share PII with third parties we contract with to process information or complete other tasks, such as shipping items.** These companies are only allowed to use your information to deliver the product or service. When we do engage a third party, we ask the vendor to sign a nondisclosure agreement. Springfield College will never share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information to third parties for their use. 

**From time to time we may receive requests to disclose the identities of our users.** We do not disclose the identities of our users unless we are legally required to do so. If a governmental agency (for example, law enforcement agencies, United States Attorneys' offices, or similar governmental agencies) sends us a subpoena, we will comply with it. 

**Information we collect may be used by Springfield College for:**

  * Educational and/or research purposes
  * Editorial and feedback purposes
  * Promotional and recruiting purposes
  * Statistical analysis of visitor behavior
  * Web site customization

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Springfield College reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice. Questions concerning this privacy policy should be directed to:**

Office of Marketing and Communications   
Springfield College   
263 Alden St.   
Springfield, MA 01109 

The rules, regulations, policies, fees, and other charges, courses of study, and admission and academic requirements that appear in this web site were in effect at the time of publication. They are published for informational purposes only, and do not constitute a contract between the College and any student, applicant for admission, or other person. 

Whether noted elsewhere in this web site or not, the College reserves the right to change, eliminate, and add to any existing (and to introduce additional) rules, regulations, policies, fees and other charges, courses of study, and academic and admission requirements. Whenever it does so, the College will give as much advance notice as it considers feasible or appropriate, but it reserves the right in all cases to do so without notice.
